

ABOUT ME

Working with some of the most important internet companies across different areas. Got full stack experience creating and managing websites, apps and GUIs from the concept stage all the way to publishing. Love learning new things and tools every day. If I do not know something I will learn it.

LINKS

Personal Site:

https://panteliskassotis.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bearofleipzig

GitHub:

https://github.com/pkassotis

Stack Overflow:

https://stackoverflow.com/users/story/8929467

SKILLS

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES: HTML5, CSS, C++, C#, JAVASCRIPT, PYTHON

IBM QUANTUM DEVELOPER

UNITY CERTIFIED DEVELOPER

STEAMWORKS DEVELOPER

PANTELIS KASSOTIS

0

Eleftheriou Venizelou 14B, Athens, 14565, Greece



(+30) 698 5033 632



info@panteliskassotis.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

BLENDER

Full-Time, Remote Jan 2020 - Present

Product Development Engineer

Blender supports the entirety of the 3D pipeline—modeling, rigging, animation, simulation, rendering, compositing and motion tracking, even video editing and game creation. I mostly fix bugs, review code and create addons using Python, and C++.

HACKERONE

Contract, Remote Mar 2020 -Present

Cyber Security Consultant

HackerOne was started by security leaders who are driven by a passion to make the internet safer. We partner with the global hacker community to surface the most relevant security issues of our customers before they can be exploited by criminals.

HUNT CLUB

Contract, Remote Dec 2020 -Present

Information Technology Recruiter

Thanks to my role at GitHub and the Open Source community in general I come in contact with talented programmers every day so it makes sense to connect them with tech companies if they happen to be open to new opportunities.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE

New York, NY 2021

MicroBachelors (MB), Computer Science Fundamentals

New York University I Tandon School of Engineering

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Cambridge, MA 2020

Advanced Professional Certifications (APCs), Web Programming, Mobile Apps, Game Development and Artificial Intelligence

<u>Harvard University I John A. Paulson School of Engine</u> <u>ering and Applied Sciences</u>

HOBBIES

SOCCER, KAYAKING, MUSIC PUBLISHING, WRITING, ANIMATION